<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>VMworld 2021 - Tag - vCROCS</title>
        <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vmworld-2021/</link>
        <description>VMworld 2021 - Tag - vCROCS</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vmworld-2021/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Year in Review - 2021 | 2022 Goals</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/look-back-2021/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/look-back-2021/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Get-Review 2021</strong></p>
<hr>
<p>2021 was a good year for me with my career. I spent the entire year working from home and I find myself to be more productive when WFH. My wife and I moved into a different home and I now have a dedicated office area on the 2nd floor away from everyone. I still share my office with Belle (Rescue Dog adopted in 2020 before covid) everyday and she loves the fenced in back yard that she can run around in without a leash.</p>
<p>In 2021, I started living the &ldquo;Salt Life&rdquo;. In July, I installed SaltStack Config for the first time and started taking a serious look at Salt. I went from zero to doing a presentation about SaltStack at VMworld 2021 in October and another presentation at SaltConf21 in November. Having a session selected for VMworld 2021 was a career &ldquo;Bucket List&rdquo; for me.</p>
<p>After creating a vRealize Operations Dashboard on &ldquo;Right Sizing&rdquo; that I use in production, my vRealize Account Executive setup a meeting for me to meet Iwan &rsquo;e1&rsquo; Rahabok, who is the co-creator of the book &ldquo;Operationalize Your World&rdquo;. Iwan liked the Dashboard I created and included some details about the Dashboard in his book &ldquo;Operationalize Your World&rdquo;.</p>
<p>I always say if one person finds anything I post helpful, I will consider my efforts successful. In 2021, between the presentations and blogs posts, I feel I have given back and helped some people. I shared the knowledge.  2021 was a successful year for me.</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="highlights-of-2021">Highlights of 2021</h6>
<ul>
<li>VMworld 2021 session (Presentation): Manage Windows Workloads Through vRealize Automation SaltStack Config [MCL1895]</li>
<li>SaltConf21 session (Presentation): Managing Windows with SaltStack Config</li>
<li>(6) of my personal Blogs were shared by the VMware &ldquo;vExpert Cloud Management Community&rdquo; on the Vmware Blog Web Site.</li>
<li>I did several vRealize Automation Presentations at VMware HVC (Healthcare Virtualization Community) Events.</li>
<li>PowerBlock Customer Showcase - VM &ldquo;Right Sizing&rdquo;</li>
<li>I did a IDC interview for VMware on Automation that will be released in 2022.</li>
<li>I did a VMware Customer Reference Interview that will be released in 2022. <a href="https://blogs.vmware.com/management/2022/03/vra-optimize-healthcare-outcomes.html" target="_blank">Link to Customer Reference</a></li>
<li>I shared a vRealize Operations &ldquo;Right Sizing&rdquo; Dashboard on the code.vmware.com web site.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h6 id="my-top-10-blog-posts-of-2021">My Top 10 Blog Posts of 2021</h6>
<ol>
<li>How to use PowerShell modules with vRA 8.2 | 978</li>
<li>How vRealize Operations can help with &ldquo;Right sizing&rdquo; VMs | 799</li>
<li>vRA 8.1 ABX PS | 508</li>
<li>Automating Automation | 415</li>
<li>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 1 | 333</li>
<li>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 2 | 280</li>
<li>vRealize automation 8.1 PowerShell abx | 216</li>
<li>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 4 | 195</li>
<li>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 6 | 164</li>
<li>VMworld 2021 SaltStack Config session | 147</li>
</ol>
<p>What the top 10 list shows me is there is a lot of interest to use PowerShell with the vRealize Products, VMware admins are interested in Right Sizing and since VMware Purchased SaltStack people what to get started with the product.</p>
<p>*Stats from Google Analytics.</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="set-goals-2022">Set-Goals 2022</h6>
<ul>
<li>I do a lot of posts on PowerShell and I use it everyday. I want to take some time in 2022 and learn Python. I have done a little bit of Python but not enough to call myself a Python Programmer. I think there are some use cases with vRealize Automation and SaltStack Config that knowing Python may help.</li>
<li>I want to spend more time with Salt. Salt is a powerful tool and I want to expand my knowledge with Salt.</li>
<li>Get a session approved for VMworld 2022 and SaltConf22.</li>
<li>Do more VMware PowerBlock Presentations.</li>
<li>Create more Blog Posts.</li>
<li>Never Stop Learning&hellip;</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h6 id="thanks-for-visiting-in-2021">Thanks for visiting in 2021!</h6>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you like wearing Crocs and want to get a pair like I wear, follow this link to Amazon:
<a target="_blank" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001V7Z27W?psc=1&amp;ref=ppx_yo2ov_dt_b_product_details&_encoding=UTF8&tag=vcrocs-20&linkCode=ur2&linkId=fa4c787c9ab59a9b8a54b48c402b8517&camp=1789&creative=9325">My Favorite Crocs</a></li>
<li>If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>VMworld 2021 - SaltStack Config Session</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Manage Windows Workloads Through vRealize Automation SaltStack Config [MCL1895]</strong></p>
<hr>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/vmworld2021-logo-horizontal.jpg" title="/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/vmworld2021-logo-horizontal.jpg" data-thumbnail="/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/vmworld2021-logo-horizontal.jpg" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image</figcaption>
    </figure>
<p>I will be doing a VMworld presentation for the first time at VMworld 2021. I have attended VMworld since 2012 and it has been a goal of mine to do a presentation at a VMworld since the first year I attended.  There are always so many good sessions to attend. We are putting many hours into this presentation so that the people attending feel it was worth their time and learn a lot about the topic. We have a awesome topic and some great presentations to show.</p>
<p>So register today for VMworld 2021 and attend my session.</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="session-name">Session Name:</h6>
<p>Manage Windows Workloads Through vRealize Automation SaltStack Config [MCL1895]</p>
<h6 id="description">Description:</h6>
<p>This session will include an overview of vRealize SaltStack Config and see how a customer in the healthcare vertical is managing their fleet of Windows systems using vRealize Automation SaltStack Config (SSC).</p>
<h6 id="presenters">Presenters:</h6>
<p>Vincent Riccio, TMM, VMware<br>
Dale Hassinger, Lead Systems Engineer - SME</p>
<p>Topic: Manage &amp; Operate Multiple Clouds<br>
Track : Multi-Cloud<br>
Primary Product: VMware vRealize Automation / vRealize Automation Cloud<br>
Primary Audience: Infrastructure Engineer<br>
Session Type: Breakout Session<br>
Level: Technical 200<br>
Pass Type: General and Tech+ Passes<br>
VMworld online conference: 10/05/2021-10/07/2021</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="link-to-session-in-vmworld-content-catalog">Link to session in VMworld Content Catalog:</h6>
<p><a href="https://www.vmware.com/vmworld/en/video-library/video-landing.html?sessionid=1621001698288001Ro2y&videoId=6274088354001" target="_blank">Manage Windows Workloads Through vRealize Automation SaltStack Config [MCL1895]</a></p>
<hr>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/vmworld-mcl1895.png" title="/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/vmworld-mcl1895.png" data-thumbnail="/vmworld-2021-mcl1895/vmworld-mcl1895.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image</figcaption>
    </figure>
<hr>
<p>In our Presentation we wil show how to use SaltStack Config to manage Microsoft Windows Servers. How to use Salt to install software, work with Windows Services, make Registry changes, configuration management, and other normal day to day Windows Server administration.</p>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
