<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VMworld 2021 on vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vmworld-2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VMworld 2021 on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vmworld-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to www.vCROCS.info</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/welcome-to-www.vcrocs.info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/welcome-to-www.vcrocs.info/</guid>
      <description>I have learned a lot from the vCommunity, Powershell and PowerCLI web sites. I want to use this blog as a way for me to give back. If one person finds anything I post helpful, I will consider my efforts successful.
 Favorite Quotes: &amp;ldquo;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to hire smart people and then tell them what to do, We hire smart people so they can tell us what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year in Review - 2021 | 2022 Goals</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/year-in-review-2021-2022-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/year-in-review-2021-2022-goals/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; Get-Review 2021  2021 was a good year for me with my career. I spent the entire year working from home and I find myself to be more productive when WFH. My wife and I moved into a different home and I now have a dedicated office area on the 2nd floor away from anyone else. I still share my office with Belle (Rescue Dog adopted in 2020 before covid) everyday and she loves the fenced in back yard that she now has access to running around in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2021 - SaltStack Config Session</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmworld-2021-saltstack-config-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmworld-2021-saltstack-config-session/</guid>
      <description>I will be doing a VMworld presentation for the first time at VMworld 2021. I have attended VMworld since 2012 and it has been a goal of mine to do a presentation at a VMworld since the first year I attended. There are always so many good sessions to attend. We are putting many hours into this presentation so that the people attending feel it was worth their time and learn a lot about the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
