<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>vExpert Cloud Management - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/04/vexpert-cloud-management-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/04/vexpert-cloud-management-2021/</guid>
      <description>vExpert Cloud Management 
I am very proud to be part of the VMware vExpert subprogram &amp;ldquo;Cloud Management&amp;rdquo;. This is the first year that I was accepted into the subprogram.
Almost all my blog posts and talks that I give are about one of the vRealize Products. The (2) Products that I use the most are vRealize Automation and Operations but I will be writing about more of the other Products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Automation</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/03/automating-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/03/automating-automation/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a use case where I wanted to execute a vRealize Orchestrator Workflow by using REST API. There is some documentation available but not a lot of details on how to get and use variables, sdk-objects and bearer token for permission. Here is how I made the vRO REST API calls with PowerShell using vRealize Orchestrator built-into vRA.
 Steps:
 Permission:  Need to get a Bearer Token from vRO to make REST API Call to execute Workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vRealize Operations 8.x - New Features</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/02/vrealize-operations-8.x-new-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/02/vrealize-operations-8.x-new-features/</guid>
      <description>Donut Charts.  This is one of my favorite new features. The donut chart allows you to show a lot of information in a smaller space and makes the Dashboards look more modern and clean looking. I have been replacing the Heat Map Widgets on some of my custom Dashboards with Donut Charts. If you click on the colors of the Donut charts you will then get a list of the data that makes up that color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vExpert 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/02/vexpert-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/02/vexpert-2021/</guid>
      <description>vExpert 2020, 2021          VMware vExpert 2020,2021    I am very proud to be part of the VMware vExpert program. This is the second year that I was accepted into the program. One part of the vExpert program that I think is great is that this recognizes people for sharing their knowledge and &amp;ldquo;Giving Back&amp;rdquo;. I have crossed paths with people throughout my career that didn&amp;rsquo;t like sharing what they know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hugo Theme for Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/02/new-hugo-theme-for-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/02/new-hugo-theme-for-blog/</guid>
      <description>I am always looking at the Hugo Themes to see if there are any new Themes that I liked more than I was currently using. I started looking at the Tranquilpeak Theme and really like how it looked and worked.
Tranquilpeak Hugo Theme
So I changed my Blog site to the new theme. This Theme works well with all the screen sizes and devices. I also like how the Theme automatically shows the order that the &amp;ldquo;Posts&amp;rdquo; and all the &amp;ldquo;TAGs&amp;rdquo; that I assign to each article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use PowerShell Modules with vRA 8.2</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-use-powershell-modules-with-vra-8.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-use-powershell-modules-with-vra-8.2/</guid>
      <description>I like to review VMware vRA (vRealize Automation) 8.2 as a Microsoft Windows Server Admin. Most of the reviews you see are creating Linux VMs and customizing the OS using tools for Linux. I create Windows/Linux VMs and customize the OS using a new feature added to vRA 8.x, Action Based Extensibility (ABX) with PowerShell.
In my vRA 7.6 environment I use a PowerShell Host to run processes and on the PowerShell Host is where I install all the PS Modules that I use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be successful with VMware vRealize Products in your environment</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-be-successful-with-vmware-vrealize-products-in-your-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-be-successful-with-vmware-vrealize-products-in-your-environment/</guid>
      <description>I often get asked to speak to different organizations about what I have accomplished with the VMware vRealize Suite of products. The one question that almost always gets asked is how are you able to do everything that you have setup in your environment. After being asked this question a lot I thought I would give my thoughts in a Blog Post. Here is my “Recipe for Success”:
Ingredients:  Enjoy what you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Charts with ChartJS and displaying in vRealize Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/creating-charts-with-chartjs-and-displaying-in-vrealize-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/creating-charts-with-chartjs-and-displaying-in-vrealize-operations/</guid>
      <description>I like the idea of using VMware vRealize Operations as the “Single Pane of Glass” for all monitoring. The Citrix Team recently asked me if I could show license usage within vRealize Operations. They wanted to see the highest usage in the last 30 days, 10 days and 24 hours. Citrix license usage is not built into vROPS but I have used the “Text Display Widget” to show other information within vROPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESXi on Raspberry PI</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/esxi-on-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/esxi-on-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <description>I have always be fascinated with everything that you can do with a Raspberry PI. When VMware released their Fling to install ESXi on the Raspberry PI I have become even more fascinated. An ESXi Host for the Home Lab for $50. Sign me up.
During VMworld 2020, VMware announced that they would be releasing a Fling to install ESXi on the Raspberry PI. Before the VMworld session was over I had a new Raspberry PI ordered and it was delivered the next day, ahead of the Fling release, so that I would be ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vBrownbag VMworld Presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/vbrownbag-vmworld-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/vbrownbag-vmworld-presentation/</guid>
      <description>How to use vRealize Operations as your monitoring &amp;ldquo;Single Pane of Glass&amp;rdquo; For the 2020 VMware VMworld my presentation for the vBrownbag TechTalks was selected.
Learn how to use the &amp;ldquo;Text Display&amp;rdquo; Widget on Dashboards to display data that is not within vRealize Operations. Display Weather Forecasts, Radar Maps, Data from SQL DBs on your next NOC Dashboard.
  Socials:  Twitter: https://twitter.com/vBrownBag Facebook: https://facebook.com/vBrownBag iTunes: http://bit.ly/vbrownbagitunes  https://vBrownBag.com is a community of people who believe in helping other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Display Widget - More Powerful than just displaying text on a Dashboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/07/text-display-widget-more-powerful-than-just-displaying-text-on-a-dashboard.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/07/text-display-widget-more-powerful-than-just-displaying-text-on-a-dashboard.../</guid>
      <description>I was recently reviewing some sample custom vRealize Operations Dashboards and I seen where some of the Dashboards had custom text and images. I reviewed how they included the text and images and in some of the sample Dashboards they used the “Text Display” Widget and used a url for the content. They would display images saved on a web server. I thought this was interesting and started reviewing what else could be displayed by using a url with the &amp;ldquo;Text Display&amp;rdquo; Widget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Desk and Homelab.</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/07/smart-desk-and-homelab./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/07/smart-desk-and-homelab./</guid>
      <description>Smart Desk: Like most people that work in the Technology Field I have been &amp;ldquo;WFH&amp;rdquo; (Working From Home) since the beginning of March. I already had a dedicated office area but it wasn’t setup for full time employment. I always liked a L-Shaped desk and I had this layout by pushing to straight desks together. Worked OK but could use improvement.
So I started looking at new desks. I had two requirements, L-Shaped and I also wanted my next desk to be a standup Desk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infoblox 1.1 plugin for vRA 8.1</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/06/infoblox-1.1-plugin-for-vra-8.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/06/infoblox-1.1-plugin-for-vra-8.1/</guid>
      <description>I recently setup the Infoblox 1.1 plugin for vRA 8.1 and ran into an interesting challenge that I thought I would share. The setup of the plugin is straight forward; follow the documentation and you’ll likely be set. However, if you use custom DNS views in Infoblox (internal, external, etc.) then some additional configuration is required that’s not easily identified. Out of the box, the Infoblox IPAM integration comes with only a few default properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is vRealize Automation - Episode 21</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/what-is-vrealize-automation-episode-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/what-is-vrealize-automation-episode-21/</guid>
      <description>I have been listening to Podcasts for many years. Everyday while driving to and from work I would listen to a Podcast. Anytime I traveled to a conference I would download hours worth of Podcasts to listen to while flying. Most of the Podcasts I listen to are Technology related. Here are some of my favorites:
 IT Reality Virtual Speaking Podcast Develop Great Managers vBrown Bag Automators Mac Power Users Twit Network of Podcasts  I have had an interest to be a guest on a Podcast for several years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vRealize Automation 8.1 - PowerShell ABX</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/vrealize-automation-8.1-powershell-abx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/vrealize-automation-8.1-powershell-abx/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to review VMware vRA (vRealize Automation) 8.x as a Microsoft Windows Server Admin. Most of the reviews you see are creating Linux VMs and customizing the OS using tools for Linux. I am going to create Windows Server VMs and customize the OS using a new feature added to vRA 8.1, Action Based Extensibility (ABX) with PowerShell. No vRO (Orchestrator) Workflows will be used. This is completely different compared to how I create Windows Servers with vRA 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Talk Tip of the week - 05/15/2020</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/coffee-talk-tip-of-the-week-05/15/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/coffee-talk-tip-of-the-week-05/15/2020/</guid>
      <description>If you have vRealize Log Insight installed in your environment you need to setup at least one alert that works awesome. When an ESXi Host has an PSOD event, it is difficult in vCenter to see all the HA events of all the VMs that restarted. The events are on the hosts were the VM restarted not the host that had the PSOD. If you have a cluster with a lot of hosts it can take some time to find all the events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Talk Tip of the week - 05/08/2020</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/coffee-talk-tip-of-the-week-05/08/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/coffee-talk-tip-of-the-week-05/08/2020/</guid>
      <description>If you need to set the ESXi Host Advanced System Setting Syslog.global.logHost on every ESXI Host in your environment here is some sample PowerCLI code to set the values. Connect to all your vCenters. Get all your hosts. Set the value and then it will reload the syslog service.
The second PowerCLI code example is to get the ESXi Host Advanced System Setting Syslog.global.logHost value on every ESXI Host in your environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Talk Tip of the week - 05/01/2020</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/coffee-talk-tip-of-the-week-05/01/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/coffee-talk-tip-of-the-week-05/01/2020/</guid>
      <description>When working in a Zero Trust Environment and programs are not working the way they should it is nice to have some Tools available to do troubleshooting. When new applications are installed and not working you can be asking yourself is it my issue with the application or is the firewall blocking ports. I recently had a support call with VMware and they showed me two commands that work awesome to test to see if ports are open to a destination IP on a specific port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/hugo/</guid>
      <description>I have reviewed and tried a lot of different ways to create a personal Blog so that I can share Code, Knowledge, Pictures and do Reviews. After spending some time with Hugo it has become the framework that I have liked the most. The Theme &amp;ldquo;Hugo Future Imperfect&amp;rdquo; is also the Hugo Theme that I have liked the most.

Some of the ways I have reviewed creating a Blog require a monthly fee to host the web site for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add disk</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/add-disk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/add-disk/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code Powershell code to add disk to a Remote Windows Server VMware VM
 #The Following code shows how to add a New Drive, bring drive online, initialize and format: #Connect to vCenter Connect-VIServer vcsa.domain.org #Add new drive to VM New-HardDisk -VM $VMNAME -CapacityGB $DISKSIZEGB -StorageFormat Thin -Controller ‘SCSI Controller 1’ #Make disk online invoke-command -computername $VMNAME -scriptblock {Set-Disk 2 -isOffline $false} #Initialize disk invoke-command -computername $VMNAME -scriptblock {Initialize-Disk 2 -PartitionStyle GPT} #Create Partition invoke-command -computername $VMNAME -scriptblock {New-Partition -DiskNumber 2 -UseMaximumSize -DriveLetter E} #Format drive invoke-command -computername $VMNAME -scriptblock {Format-Volume -DriveLetter E -FileSystem NTFS -NewFileSystemLabel ‘Data’ -AllocationUnitSize 16384 -Confirm:$false} #------------------------------------------------------------------------- #The Following Code will show disk “Allocation Unit Size” on a remote Windows Server: $C = Invoke-Command -ComputerName $VMname {Get-WmiObject -Class Win32_Volume -Filter “DriveLetter = ‘C:&#39;” | Select-Object BLOCKSIZE} $C_AllocationUnitSize = ($C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Registry Values</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/add-registry-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/add-registry-values/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code Add Registry Values to Windows Server
 #vCrocs Registry Changes invoke-command -computername $FQDNVMname -ScriptBlock {new-Item HKLM:\SOFTWARE\vCrocs -f } invoke-command -computername $FQDNVMname -ScriptBlock {param ($SG) Set-ItemProperty hklm:\software\vCrocs -Name SupportGroup -Value &amp;quot;$SG&amp;quot; -Force} -ArgumentList $SG invoke-command -computername $FQDNVMname -ScriptBlock {param ($APP) Set-ItemProperty hklm:\software\vCrocs -Name Application -Value &amp;quot;$APP&amp;quot; -Force} -ArgumentList $APP invoke-command -computername $FQDNVMname -ScriptBlock {param ($LOC) Set-ItemProperty hklm:\software\vCrocs -Name Location -Value &amp;quot;$LOC&amp;quot; -Force} -ArgumentList $LOC invoke-command -computername $FQDNVMname -ScriptBlock {param ($SL) Set-ItemProperty hklm:\software\vCrocs -Name ServiceLevel -Value &amp;quot;$SL&amp;quot; -Force} -ArgumentList $SL </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automation with Zero Trust</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/automation-with-zero-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/automation-with-zero-trust/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code There are two PowerCLI commands that have become my best friends in a Zero Trust Environment.
 Invoke-VMScript - Use to run scripts on VMs. Copy-VMGuestFile - Use to copy files to/from VMs.  In this example you can use Invoke-VMScript to run commands on a VM to install Trend Deep Security. All commands run with VM in a zero trust state.
 $VMName = &#39;VM Name&#39; #Copy file to the VM $PSText = &#39;wget https://server01.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSX PowerCLI Basics</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/nsx-powercli-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/nsx-powercli-basics/</guid>
      <description>NSX PowerCLI Code Some basic PowerCLI commands with NSX
Included some examples of code to Automate adding/removing NSX Security Tags from VMs.
 Show Security TAGs. Show Security TAGs assigned to a specific VM.  Hope you find these snippets of code useful.
 # Need to install PowerShell Module PowerNSX # Connect to vCenter $vCenterName = &#39;vCenter.vCrocs.info&#39; Connect-VIServer $vCenterName -Credential $cred # Connect to NSX Server Connect-NsxServer -vCenterServer &#39;vCenter.vCrocs.info&#39; -Credential $cred # Show all Security Tags Get-NsxSecurityTag | Select-Object Name | Sort-Object Name # Info about one specific Security TAG Get-NsxSecurityTag -Name NSX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/open-ports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/open-ports/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code Use PowerShell to see if ports are open to a remote server.
 $PortNumber = &#39;443&#39; $Destination = &#39;Server.vCrocs.info&#39; $socket = New-Object Net.Sockets.TcpClient $socket.Connect($Destination,$PortNumber) if($socket.Connected){ $PortOpened = &#39;Port: &#39; + $PortNumber + &#39; to &#39; + $Destination +&#39; is Open! :)&#39; $socket.Close() }else{ $PortOpened = &#39;Port: &#39; + $PortNumber + &#39; to &#39; + $Destination +&#39; IS NOT Open! :(&#39; } Write-Host $PortOpened Living in a zero trust environment can be challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerCLI Basics</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/powercli-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/powercli-basics/</guid>
      <description>PowerCLI Code Some basic PowerCLI commands
 #Here are some basic commands that you can keep adding additional code #and get more precise on what you want to see. #Connect to a vCenter Connect-VIServer vcsa.domain.org #Disconnect from vCenter and not be prompted Disconnect-VIServer vcsa.domain.org -confirm:$false #Get VM Listing #Shows all VMs Get-VM #Shows all VMs sorted by Name Get-VM | Sort-Object Name #Shows all VMs sorted by Name that are Powered On Get-VM | Where-Object {$_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Log Files</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/powershell-log-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/powershell-log-files/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code I use this code to create a log file during a VM build using vRealize Automation
Here&amp;rsquo;s an example:
 $VMname = &#39;ServerName&#39; #The next line defines where to save the log file $LOGFILENAME = &amp;quot;C:\vRA-Install-Logs\vRA-Install-Log-&amp;quot; + $VMname + &amp;quot;.log&amp;quot; #Check to see if file already exists. If it does delete it. if (Test-Path $LOGFILENAME) { Remove-Item -Path $LOGFILENAME } #Creates the Log File New-Item $LOGFILENAME -ItemType File #Update Log File.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Randon Password</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/randon-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/randon-password/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code I use this code to generate a random password during the automation process of creating a new Server VM. I then add the password to Password Manager with Powershell.
 #Generate Random text to use for Password $SQLPassword =@( [char[]](65..91 | Get-Random -Count 5) [char[]](97..123 | Get-Random -Count 5) &#39;!&#39;,&#39;#&#39;,&#39;(&#39;,&#39;)&#39; | Get-Random -Count 2 0..9 | Get-Random -Count 4 ) | Sort-Object {Get-Random} $Password = $SQLPassword -join &#39;&#39; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry PI Powered Clay Thrower</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/raspberry-pi-powered-clay-thrower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/raspberry-pi-powered-clay-thrower/</guid>
      <description>Raspberry PI Powered Clay Thrower Link to my Raspberry PI powered Clay Thrower. The first project I ever did with a PI. My first project using Python and PHP.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule RVTools</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/schedule-rvtools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/04/schedule-rvtools/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code I like to create a Scheduled Task in vRealize Orchestrator to create RVtools files everyday. Here is a sample script that could be used. The script is also on a 7 day rotation of files and automaticaly deletes old files.
 Start-Process -FilePath &amp;quot;C:\Program Files (x86)\Robware\RVTools\RVtools.exe&amp;quot; -ArgumentList &#39;-s vCenter01.vCrocs.info -u administrator@vsphere.local -p &amp;quot;Enter RVTools encrypted Password between the double quotes&amp;quot; -c Exportall2xls -d &amp;quot;G:\RVTools\vCenter01&amp;quot;&#39; -Wait Start-Process -FilePath &amp;quot;C:\Program Files (x86)\Robware\RVTools\RVtools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Dale Hassinger</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/01/about-dale-hassinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/01/about-dale-hassinger/</guid>
      <description>Lead Systems Engineer, SME, vExpert 2020, 2021 If you can script it, You can Automate it&amp;hellip;          VMware vExpert 2020,2021    Email: Dale.Hassinger@vCrocs.info
Location: Mechanicsburg, PA
My current focus is Enterprise Automation, Monitoring and Logging. I am using VMware vRealize Automation to complete server builds, software installs, schedule VM snap shots, Microsoft 365 automation, Citrix Management, Automate Data Center Flips, Server Decommissions, and many other Day 2 processes&amp;hellip; For monitoring I use vRealize Operations for the &amp;ldquo;Single Pane of Glass&amp;rdquo; experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery - Dale Favorites</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/01/image-gallery-dale-favorites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/01/image-gallery-dale-favorites/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image Gallery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
