<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vRealize Operations on vCrocs.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vrealize-operations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vRealize Operations on vCrocs.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vrealize-operations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Charts with ChartJS and displaying in vRealize Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/creating-charts-with-chartjs-and-displaying-in-vrealize-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/creating-charts-with-chartjs-and-displaying-in-vrealize-operations/</guid>
      <description>I like the idea of using VMware vRealize Operations as the “Single Pane of Glass” for all monitoring. The Citrix Team recently asked me if I could show license usage within vRealize Operations. They wanted to see the highest usage in the last 30 days, 10 days and 24 hours. Citrix license usage is not built into vROPS but I have used the “Text Display Widget” to show other information within vROPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESXi on Raspberry PI</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/esxi-on-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/esxi-on-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <description>I have always be fascinated with everything that you can do with a Raspberry PI. When VMware released their Fling to install ESXi on the Raspberry PI I have become even more fascinated. An ESXi Host for the Home Lab for $50. Sign me up.
During VMworld 2020, VMware announced that they would be releasing a Fling to install ESXi on the Raspberry PI. Before the VMworld session was over I had a new Raspberry PI ordered and it was delivered the next day, ahead of the Fling release, so that I would be ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vBrownbag VMworld Presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/vbrownbag-vmworld-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/vbrownbag-vmworld-presentation/</guid>
      <description>How to use vRealize Operations as your monitoring &amp;ldquo;Single Pane of Glass&amp;rdquo; For the 2020 VMware VMworld my presentation for the vBrownbag TechTalks was selected.
Learn how to use the &amp;ldquo;Text Display&amp;rdquo; Widget on Dashboards to display data that is not within vRealize Operations. Display Weather Forecasts, Radar Maps, Data from SQL DBs on your next NOC Dashboard.
  Socials:  Twitter: https://twitter.com/vBrownBag Facebook: https://facebook.com/vBrownBag iTunes: http://bit.ly/vbrownbagitunes  https://vBrownBag.com is a community of people who believe in helping other people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>