<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Vegas - Tag - vCROCS</title>
        <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vegas/</link>
        <description>Vegas - Tag - vCROCS</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vegas/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>VMware Explore 2024 | My Sessions</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/vmware-explore-2024-sessions/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/vmware-explore-2024-sessions/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>I am presenting (3) sessions at VMware Explore 2024.</strong></p>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>&ldquo;Technology can amplify your message, but the real power of a presentation lies in the connection you make with your audience. Remember, it&rsquo;s not the slides or the software that will leave a lasting impact—it&rsquo;s your passion and the story you tell.&rdquo; - ChatGPT</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<h6 id="my-vmware-explore-2024-sessions">My VMware Explore 2024 Sessions</h6>
<p><strong>When and Where:</strong><br>
Website: <a href="https://www.vmware.com/explore/us" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024.</a><br>
Las Vegas Date: August 26 – 29, 2024<br>
The Venetian Convention and Expo Center</p>
<hr>
<p>I&rsquo;m thrilled to announce that I will be presenting three sessions at VMware Explore 2024! My journey to this moment began at the Mid-Atlantic HVC (Healthcare Virtualization Community) events. I initially attended these events as a VMware customer eager to learn. Eventually, I was invited to present on the automation work I was doing with VMware Products. Though nerve-wracking, my first presentation was a success, and the positive feedback encouraged me to start my blog, sharing knowledge with the vCommunity.</p>
<p>After countless blog posts and community events, I&rsquo;m now honored to present a General Session at VMware Explore 2024. For those in the VMware community, this is the pinnacle of recognition and opportunity. I&rsquo;m excited to bring my passion for VMware products to these sessions, and I invite you to sign up and join me. I&rsquo;ll do my best to share valuable insights and help you enhance your environments. Check out the links to my sessions below and in the <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=Hassinger" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024 Content Catalog</a>. Hope to see you in Vegas!</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="sessions">Sessions:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Streamlining Healthcare with Automation: How VMware Can Help | <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=INDB1917LV" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">INDB1917LV</a>
<ul>
<li>In this session, learn to elevate your automation game. Join us to discover practical strategies for boosting your team&rsquo;s efficiency. 1) Automate Windows and Linux VM builds 2) Streamline Day 2 tasks like snapshots and reboots 3) Enhance security incident management by configuring Aria Operations for Logs to alert on log analysis, and 4) Automate snapshot deletion and power operations using Aria Operations Automation Central.</li>
<li>I&rsquo;m excited to announce that <strong>Don Horrox</strong>, Systems Engineer, will be co-presenting with me in this session. I met Don when he was a VMware customer that I worked with and was immediately impressed by his passion for VMware products. Together, we have prepared some great content to share with everyone on their automation journey. Check out Don&rsquo;s blog, <a href="https://vchamp.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">vChamp</a>, to see what he has been sharing with the vCommunity.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Transform VCF Automation Inputs to ABX and Orchestrator Workflow Variables | <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=CODE1164LV" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">CODE1164LV</a>
<ul>
<li>Master the art of converting any VCF Aria Automation template input into a dynamic variable for ABX or Orchestrator Workflows. This session will guide you through the process of turning inputs into versatile properties, ready to be integrated as parameters for any script. Unlock the potential to automate virtually any task within your infrastructure. By the end of this session, you&rsquo;ll realize that your creativity in variable use is the most powerful automation tool at your disposal.</li>
<li>After attending this session, you&rsquo;ll be inspired to automate everything in your environment. Discover how easy it is to automate any task. Your thought process will become the most powerful automation tool you&rsquo;ll have after this session.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Maximizing VMware Workstation/Fusion for Business, Education, and Home Labs | <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=CODE1162LV" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">CODE1162LV</a>
<ul>
<li>Explore the versatility of VMware Workstation and Fusion for diverse applications within your setup. Discover my personal methodology for leveraging Workstation/Fusion to evaluate software on virtual machines, conduct nested ESXi for educational purposes, or operate Linux VMs on Windows or Mac laptops. Delve into the included Workstation/Fusion APIs as a resource for automation education. I&rsquo;ll demo PowerShell Functions I developed, using the APIs, for efficient VM management on Workstation/Fusion.</li>
<li>My goal with this session is to assist everyone from beginners in virtualization to those looking to enhance their daily automation tasks. You&rsquo;ll learn how to set up a powerful home lab and leverage APIs to advance your coding skills.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p><a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=Hassinger" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to all my sessions in the VMware Explore 2024 Content Catalog</a></p>
<hr>
<h6 id="session-details">Session Details:</h6>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/vmware-explore-2024-sessions/vmware-explore-2024-01.png" title="/vmware-explore-2024-sessions/vmware-explore-2024-01.png" data-thumbnail="/vmware-explore-2024-sessions/vmware-explore-2024-01.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</figcaption>
    </figure>
<hr>
<h6 id="links-to-resources-discussed-is-this-blog-post">Links to resources discussed is this Blog Post:</h6>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.vmware.com/explore/us" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024.</a></li>
<li><a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/reg/login" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024 | Registration Link.</a></li>
</ul>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you found this blog article helpful and it assisted you, consider buying me a coffee to kickstart my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>
<hr>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>VMware Explore 2024</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/vmware-explore-2024/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/vmware-explore-2024/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Why I enjoy going to VMware Explore. First as a Customer. Now as a Employee.</strong></p>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>&ldquo;Innovate like a startup, deliver like an enterprise” - Pat Gelsinger</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<h6 id="vmware-explore-2024">VMware Explore 2024</h6>
<p>Website: <a href="https://www.vmware.com/explore/us" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024.</a><br>
Las Vegas Date: August 26 – 29, 2024<br>
The Venetian Convention and Expo Center<br>
Registration is open!</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="why-attend">Why Attend</h6>
<p><strong>When I was a VMware Customer, I tried to go to VMware Explore every year. Here is a list of reasons why I enjoyed the conference:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>To meet other people in the same field as myself. Exchange stories, ideas, contact information, etc.. The Community side of the event alone, is worth the cost to go.</li>
<li>To attend sessions that are done by people that you follow their blogs or socials, is an exciting experience.</li>
<li>The Key Note Sessions get you excited to see what is coming with the next releases of the VMware Products.</li>
<li>Vendor Parties are a great way to meet people and have good food and drink.</li>
<li>Other Highlights for evening Parties for me:
<ul>
<li>vExpert Party</li>
<li>VMUG Party</li>
<li>Event Concert on the last night (Black Keys Concert was my favorite)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p><strong>As a Employee my reasons are different to attend. Here is a list:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>To meet people in person that I work with everyday. We are located across the country and don&rsquo;t get to meet in person. Even if we went into a office everyday, we would never get to meet.</li>
<li>Get Sessions accepted and share the knowledge with the products I work with every day. I like doing presentations on the Automation, Monitoring and Logging Products.</li>
<li>I like to participate in the Hackathon that is part of the conference. In 2023 my Team received 2nd place.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h6 id="sessions">Sessions</h6>
<p>I submitted a couple sessions that hope get accepted in 2024, Fingers Crossed. One session I will be presenting with a customer, and 2 sessions I included TAMs to present with me. I am excited about the topics. When the sessions get announced, check back on this blog. I will update what was accepted.</p>
<hr>
<h6 id="sessions-update">Sessions Update!</h6>
<p>I am very excited to announce that I will be doing (3) presentations at VMware Explore 2024.</p>
<ul>
<li>Streamlining Healthcare with Automation: How VMware Can Help | <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=INDB1917LV" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">INDB1917LV</a></li>
<li>Transform VCF Automation Inputs to ABX and Orchestrator Workflow Variables | <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=CODE1164LV" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">CODE1164LV</a></li>
<li>Maximizing VMware Workstation/Fusion for Business, Education, and Home Labs | <a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=CODE1162LV" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">CODE1162LV</a></li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p><a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/content/page/catalog?search=Hassinger" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to all my sessions in the VMware Explore 2024 Content Catalog</a></p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Session Details:</strong></p>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/vmware-explore-2024/vmware-explore-2024-01.png" title="/vmware-explore-2024/vmware-explore-2024-01.png" data-thumbnail="/vmware-explore-2024/vmware-explore-2024-01.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</figcaption>
    </figure>
<hr>
<h6 id="my-favorite-places-to-eat-or-things-to-do-while-at-vmware-explore">My favorite places to eat or things to do while at VMware Explore:</h6>
<p><strong>Eating - Places that I have gone and enjoyed:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.joes.net/las-vegas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Joes&rsquo;s Prime Steak and Stone Crab</a> - I have always had a great experience here</li>
<li><a href="https://www.venetianlasvegas.com/restaurants/delmonico-steakhouse.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Delmonico Steakhouse</a> - You can&rsquo;t leave without having EMERIL’S BANANA CREAM PIE!</li>
<li><a href="https://www.venetianlasvegas.com/restaurants/grand-lux-cafe-palazzo.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Grand Lux Café at The Palazzo</a> is great for Breakfast!</li>
<li><a href="https://www.venetianlasvegas.com/restaurants/yardbird.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Yardbird</a> is close to conference entrance and food to very good</li>
<li><a href="https://www.in-n-out.com/menu" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">IN-N-Out BURGER</a> | If you live in the US East and have never gone to an IN-N-Out BURGER, you need to go at least one time.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Things to do that I have done and enjoyed:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.usbr.gov/lc/hooverdam/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Hoover Damn</a> was nice to go see. Pictures can&rsquo;t replace a visit in person.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.clarkcountynv.gov/government/departments/parks___recreation/shooting_complex/guest_services.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Sporting Clays at Clark County Shooting Complex</a> - World-Class Shotgun Center</li>
<li><a href="https://www.blm.gov/programs/national-conservation-lands/nevada/red-rock-canyon" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Red Rock Canyon National Conservation Area</a></li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h6 id="links-to-resources-discussed-is-this-blog-post">Links to resources discussed is this Blog Post:</h6>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.vmware.com/explore/us" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024.</a></li>
<li><a href="https://event.vmware.com/flow/vmware/explore2024lv/reg/login" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">VMware Explore 2024 | Registration Link.</a></li>
</ul>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you found this blog article helpful and it assisted you, consider buying me a coffee to kickstart my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>
<hr>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
