<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>IT Reality - Tag - vCROCS</title>
        <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/it-reality/</link>
        <description>IT Reality - Tag - vCROCS</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/it-reality/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>What is vRealize Automation - Episode 21</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/it-reality/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/it-reality/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>IT Reality Podcast</strong></p>
<hr>
<h6 id="podcasts">Podcasts</h6>
<p>I have been listening to Podcasts for many years.  Everyday while driving to and from work I would listen to a Podcast. Anytime I traveled to a conference I would download hours worth of Podcasts to listen to while flying. Most of the Podcasts I listen to are Technology related. Here are some of my favorites:</p>
<ul>
<li>IT Reality</li>
<li>Virtual Speaking Podcast</li>
<li>Develop Great Managers</li>
<li>vBrown Bag</li>
<li>Automators</li>
<li>Mac Power Users</li>
<li>Twit Network of Podcasts</li>
</ul>
<p>I have had an interest to be a guest on a Podcast for several years.  I always thought to myself, when I get to a point in my career that I could share my knowledge, I would try and be a guest on a Podcast.  After doing several presentations about VMware vRealize Automation, I wanted the next step to be a guest spot on a Podcast to reach a larger audience.  When I saw a post on Twitter that the IT Reality Podcast was looking for everyday Technology people passionate about a topic and willing to share the knowledge, I reached out to them to show my interest in appearing on their Podcast.  We had a meeting and the Hosts felt I had a good story to tell, so we scheduled a time to record the Podcast.  The hosts, Vince Wood and Sam Larch, were awesome to work with. They also invited Nathan Bennett to be on the episode as a guest and he was also great to talk with.  The experience to talk with these guys was a good way for me to appear on a Podcast. While recording the Podcast I learned some knowledge from Nathan that I will use in my current Automation environment.</p>
<p>If it wasn’t for other people sharing knowledge by creating Blogging web sites or appearing on Podcasts, I wouldn’t have the knowledge that I do today.  I hope that I can give back to the vCommunity like they have done for me. I would encourage anyone who wants to share their knowledge to Just Do It!  Create a Blogging Web Site or start attending local User Groups and “Little Hacks”. It can be very rewarding.</p>
<hr>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/it-reality/it-reality.png" title="/it-reality/it-reality.png" data-thumbnail="/it-reality/it-reality.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image</figcaption>
    </figure>
<h6 id="link-to-episode">Link to Episode</h6>
<p><a href="https://itr-it-reality.zencast.website/episodes/21" target="_blank">What is vRealize Automation - Episode 21</a></p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you like wearing Crocs and want to get a pair like I wear, follow this link to Amazon:
<a target="_blank" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001V7Z27W?psc=1&amp;ref=ppx_yo2ov_dt_b_product_details&_encoding=UTF8&tag=vcrocs-20&linkCode=ur2&linkId=fa4c787c9ab59a9b8a54b48c402b8517&camp=1789&creative=9325">My Favorite Crocs</a></li>
<li>If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
