<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SaltStack on vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/saltstack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SaltStack on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/saltstack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 7</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-7/</guid>
      <description>Part 7:
The more I use VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin the more I see the importance of having grain information added to the minion to be able to target servers many different ways. During a recent discussion it was suggested to have the ability to target Windows Server minions by the Windows server Features|Roles that were installed on the server and by which software was installed on a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SaltConf 2021 - Presentation Replay</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/11/saltconf-2021-presentation-replay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/11/saltconf-2021-presentation-replay/</guid>
      <description>I did SaltConf presentation for the first time at SaltConf 2021. Here is a replay of the video if you want to watch. Hope you enjoy and learn something.
    Session Details:
 Date: November 4th. Time: 10:00 am - 10:50 am Details: Track 1 - Managing Windows with SaltStack Config Presenters: Vincent Riccio and Dale Hassinger   In this Presentation we showed how to use SaltStack Config to manage Microsoft Windows Servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 6</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-6/</guid>
      <description>Part 6:
        The latest item on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin is going to be a lot PowerShell. I use PowerShell for a lot of Automation, Windows Server and Linux Server. When working with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config I constantly found myself going to the CLI to test and learn how the salt functions work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SaltConf 2021 - SaltStack Config Session</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/saltconf-2021-saltstack-config-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/saltconf-2021-saltstack-config-session/</guid>
      <description>I will be doing a SaltConf presentation for the first time at SaltConf 2021. I attended SaltConf 2020 for the first time after VMware purchased SaltStack Config. This past year I have spent a lot of time reviewing SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin and I am excited to share what I have learned to hopefully help some Windows Server Admins get started.
I wanted to learn one of the configuration Management products for a couple of years and after VMware purchased SaltStack Config the decision became obvious to me which one I should learn since I live in VMware vRealize Products all day, every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Part 5:
 The latest item on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin will be an update to some items that I have talked about in previous posts. I have been spending more time with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config and I have learned some better ways to do some of the processes that I have talked about already. My goal to to learn and use the built-in functions that are already in the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/09/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/09/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Part 4:
 The latest item on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin will be salt grains. I have a specific use case that made me start looking at grains. In VMware vCenter I use vCenter TAGs to organize VMs. I also use vCenter TAGs to organize VMs in vRealize Operations. I want to use the same logic of using vCenter TAGs in SaltStack Config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Part 3:
 The next steps on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin will be beacons and reactors. Working with Jobs helped me understand how to make changes Ad-Hoc. I have a Job to quickly stop the Print Spooler but what if I always want the state of the Print Spooler Service to be stopped. How do I NOT allow a Server Admin to login into the server and manually start the service?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2021 - SaltStack Config Session</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmworld-2021-saltstack-config-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmworld-2021-saltstack-config-session/</guid>
      <description>I will be doing a VMworld presentation for the first time at VMworld 2021. I have attended VMworld since 2012 and it has been a goal of mine to do a presentation at a VMworld since the first year I attended. There are always so many good sessions to attend. We are putting many hours into this presentation so that the people attending feel it was worth their time and learn a lot about the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Part 2:
 I have been able to spend more time with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config. Here are some updates on my journey with SaltStack as a Windows Server Admin.
  Auto-Accept new minions:  I wanted new Windows Server builds (minions) to be auto accepted into SaltStack Config instead of someone manually approving new minions. To do this you need to have a reactor.conf file. I created the file in SaltStack Config File Server in base/reactor/reactor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/07/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/07/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Part 1:
 I have recently started looking at using VMware vRealize SaltStack Config. This blog is a work in progress on my journey with Salt. I started at zero and let&amp;rsquo;s see what I discover as I work towards getting to PROD. So if this topic is interesting to you, check back often.
I wanted to learn one of the server configuration products that are available like Salt, Puppet, Chef, Ansible, etc&amp;hellip; but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure which would be the best choice long term.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
