<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dashboard on vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/dashboard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dashboard on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/dashboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How vRealize Operations can help with Right Sizing VMs</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/05/how-vrealize-operations-can-help-with-right-sizing-vms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/05/how-vrealize-operations-can-help-with-right-sizing-vms/</guid>
      <description>vRealize Operations does a good job to show you what the correct number for vCPU/Memory settings should be based on monitoring history. But instead of showing APP owners a screen that just shows what the current VM vCPU/Memory settings are and what the new settings &amp;ldquo;Should&amp;rdquo; be, I wanted to show the real data that proves why these changes should be made. It can still be hard for people to understand that taking away a VM resources can make performance better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Charts with ChartJS and displaying in vRealize Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/creating-charts-with-chartjs-and-displaying-in-vrealize-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/creating-charts-with-chartjs-and-displaying-in-vrealize-operations/</guid>
      <description>I like the idea of using VMware vRealize Operations as the “Single Pane of Glass” for all monitoring. The Citrix Team recently asked me if I could show license usage within vRealize Operations. They wanted to see the highest usage in the last 30 days, 10 days and 24 hours. Citrix license usage is not built into vROPS but I have used the “Text Display Widget” to show other information within vROPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vBrownbag VMworld Presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/vbrownbag-vmworld-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/10/vbrownbag-vmworld-presentation/</guid>
      <description>How to use vRealize Operations as your monitoring &amp;ldquo;Single Pane of Glass&amp;rdquo; For the 2020 VMware VMworld my presentation for the vBrownbag TechTalks was selected.
Learn how to use the &amp;ldquo;Text Display&amp;rdquo; Widget on Dashboards to display data that is not within vRealize Operations. Display Weather Forecasts, Radar Maps, Data from SQL DBs on your next NOC Dashboard.
  Socials:  Twitter: https://twitter.com/vBrownBag Facebook: https://facebook.com/vBrownBag iTunes: http://bit.ly/vbrownbagitunes  https://vBrownBag.com is a community of people who believe in helping other people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
