<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation on vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Automation on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/09/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/09/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Part 4:
 The latest item on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin will be salt grains. I have a specific use case that made me start looking at grains. In VMware vCenter I use vCenter TAGs to organize VMs. I also use vCenter TAGs to organize VMs in vRealize Operations. I want to use the same logic of using vCenter TAGs in SaltStack Config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Part 3:
 The next steps on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin will be beacons and reactors. Working with Jobs helped me understand how to make changes Ad-Hoc. I have a Job to quickly stop the Print Spooler but what if I always want the state of the Print Spooler Service to be stopped. How do I NOT allow a Server Admin to login into the server and manually start the service?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2021 - SaltStack Config Session</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmworld-2021-saltstack-config-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmworld-2021-saltstack-config-session/</guid>
      <description>I will be doing a VMworld presentation for the first time at VMworld 2021. I have attended VMworld since 2012 and it has been a goal of mine to do a presentation at a VMworld since the first year I attended. There are always so many good sessions to attend. We are putting many hours into this presentation so that the people attending feel it was worth their time and learn a lot about the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/08/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Part 2:
 I have been able to spend more time with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config. Here are some updates on my journey with SaltStack as a Windows Server Admin.
  Auto-Accept new minions:  I wanted new Windows Server builds (minions) to be auto accepted into SaltStack Config instead of someone manually approving new minions. To do this you need to have a reactor.conf file. I created the file in SaltStack Config File Server in base/reactor/reactor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/07/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/07/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Part 1:
 I have recently started looking at using VMware vRealize SaltStack Config. This blog is a work in progress on my journey with Salt. I started at zero and let&amp;rsquo;s see what I discover as I work towards getting to PROD. So if this topic is interesting to you, check back often.
I wanted to learn one of the server configuration products that are available like Salt, Puppet, Chef, Ansible, etc&amp;hellip; but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure which would be the best choice long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Automation (Updated)</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/04/automating-automation-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/04/automating-automation-updated/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a use case where I wanted to execute a vRealize Orchestrator Workflow by using REST API. There is some documentation available but not a lot of details on how to get and use variables, sdk-objects and bearer token for permission. Here is how I made the vRO REST API calls with PowerShell using vRealize Orchestrator built-into vRA.
 Steps:
 Permission:  Need to get a Bearer Token from vRO to make REST API Call to execute Workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule RVTools Data Export</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/04/schedule-rvtools-data-export/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/04/schedule-rvtools-data-export/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell Code I like to create a Scheduled Task in vRealize Orchestrator to create RVTools files everyday. Here is a sample PowerShell script that could be used. The script is also on a 7 day rotation of files and automatically deletes old files.
 Start-Process -FilePath &amp;quot;C:\Program Files (x86)\Robware\RVTools\RVtools.exe&amp;quot; -ArgumentList &#39;-s vCenter01.vCrocs.info -u administrator@vsphere.local -p &amp;quot;Enter RVTools encrypted Password between the double quotes&amp;quot; -c Exportall2xls -d &amp;quot;G:\RVTools\vCenter01&amp;quot;&#39; -Wait Start-Process -FilePath &amp;quot;C:\Program Files (x86)\Robware\RVTools\RVtools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
