<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vRealize Automation on vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vrealize-automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vRealize Automation on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vrealize-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automating Automation</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/03/automating-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/03/automating-automation/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a use case where I wanted to execute a vRealize Orchestrator Workflow by using REST API. There is some documentation available but not a lot of details on how to get and use variables, sdk-objects and bearer token for permission. Here is how I made the vRO REST API calls with PowerShell using vRealize Orchestrator built-into vRA.
Steps:
 Permission:  Need to get a Bearer Token from vRO to make REST API Call to execute Workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use PowerShell Modules with vRA 8.2</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-use-powershell-modules-with-vra-8.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-use-powershell-modules-with-vra-8.2/</guid>
      <description>I like to review VMware vRA (vRealize Automation) 8.2 as a Microsoft Windows Server Admin. Most of the reviews you see are creating Linux VMs and customizing the OS using tools for Linux. I create Windows/Linux VMs and customize the OS using a new feature added to vRA 8.x, Action Based Extensibility (ABX) with PowerShell.
In my vRA 7.6 environment I use a PowerShell Host to run processes and on the PowerShell Host is where I install all the PS Modules that I use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vRealize Automation 8.1 - PowerShell ABX</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/vrealize-automation-8.1-powershell-abx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/vrealize-automation-8.1-powershell-abx/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to review VMware vRA (vRealize Automation) 8.x as a Microsoft Windows Server Admin. Most of the reviews you see are creating Linux VMs and customizing the OS using tools for Linux. I am going to create Windows Server VMs and customize the OS using a new feature added to vRA 8.1, Action Based Extensibility (ABX) with PowerShell. No vRO (Orchestrator) Workflows will be used. This is completely different compared to how I create Windows Servers with vRA 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Dale Hassinger</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/01/about-dale-hassinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/01/about-dale-hassinger/</guid>
      <description>Lead Systems Engineer, SME, vExpert 2020, 2021 If you can script it, You can Automate it&amp;hellip;          VMware vExpert 2020,2021    Email: Dale.Hassinger@vCrocs.info
Location: Mechanicsburg, PA
My current focus is Enterprise Automation, Monitoring and Logging. I am using VMware vRealize Automation to complete server builds, software installs, schedule VM snap shots, Microsoft 365 automation, Citrix Management, Automate Data Center Flips, Server Decommissions, and many other Day 2 processes&amp;hellip; For monitoring I use vRealize Operations for the &amp;ldquo;Single Pane of Glass&amp;rdquo; experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
