<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vRealize Automation on vCrocs.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vrealize-automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vRealize Automation on vCrocs.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/vrealize-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use PowerShell Modules with vRA 8.2</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-use-powershell-modules-with-vra-8.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/01/how-to-use-powershell-modules-with-vra-8.2/</guid>
      <description>I like to review VMware vRA (vRealize Automation) 8.2 as a Microsoft Windows Server Admin. Most of the reviews you see are creating Linux VMs and customizing the OS using tools for Linux. I create Windows/Linux VMs and customize the OS using a new feature added to vRA 8.x, Action Based Extensibility (ABX) with PowerShell.
In my vRA 7.6 environment I use a PowerShell Host to run processes and on the PowerShell Host is where I install all the PS Modules that I use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vRealize Automation 8.1 - PowerShell ABX</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/vrealize-automation-8.1-powershell-abx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2020/05/vrealize-automation-8.1-powershell-abx/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to review VMware vRA (vRealize Automation) 8.x as a Microsoft Windows Server Admin. Most of the reviews you see are creating Linux VMs and customizing the OS using tools for Linux. I am going to create Windows Server VMs and customize the OS using a new feature added to vRA 8.1, Action Based Extensibility (ABX) with PowerShell. No vRO (Orchestrator) Workflows will be used. This is completely different compared to how I create Windows Servers with vRA 7.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>