<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>VMware VExpert 2020 - 22 on Dale Hassinger</title>
        <link>https://vcrocs.info/tags/vmware-vexpert-2020---22/</link>
        <description>Recent content in VMware VExpert 2020 - 22 on Dale Hassinger</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>vCROCS</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vcrocs.info/tags/vmware-vexpert-2020---22/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>vExpert 2022 | vExpert Cloud Management</title>
        <link>https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/featured-image.png" alt="Featured image of post vExpert 2022 | vExpert Cloud Management" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;VMware vExpert 2020 - 2022 | VMware vExpert Cloud Management 2021 - 2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;vmware-vexpert-2020---2022--vmware-vexpert-cloud-management-2021---2022&#34;&gt;VMware vExpert 2020 - 2022 | VMware vExpert Cloud Management 2021 - 2022
&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-2022-01.png&#34;
	width=&#34;250&#34;
	height=&#34;170&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-2022-01_hu11938431909810691265.png 480w, https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-2022-01_hu15755923988455194544.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;147&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;352px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-2022-3-stars.png&#34;
	width=&#34;250&#34;
	height=&#34;169&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-2022-3-stars_hu17226531154530233699.png 480w, https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-2022-3-stars_hu14996745724045607671.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;147&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;355px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-cloud-management.png&#34;
	width=&#34;250&#34;
	height=&#34;165&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-cloud-management_hu8282268011995179412.png 480w, https://vcrocs.info/vexpert-2022-vexpert-cloud-management/vexpert-cloud-management_hu10992711771605134141.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;151&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;363px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am very proud to be part of the VMware vExpert program.  This is the third year that I was accepted into the program. One part of the vExpert program that I think is great is that the program recognizes people for sharing their knowledge and &amp;ldquo;Giving Back&amp;rdquo;. A person selected into the vExpert programs is someone that likes to share, wants to make themselves and everyone around them smarter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2022 is also the 2nd year that I was accepted into the VMware vExpert Cloud Management subprogram.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that 2021 was one of my most productive years and one that I advanced my own personal knowledge the most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;highlights-of-2021-to-get-accepted-into-the-vexpert-program&#34;&gt;Highlights of 2021 to get accepted into the vExpert Program:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMworld 2021 session (Presentation): Manage Windows Workloads Through vRealize Automation SaltStack Config [MCL1895]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SaltConf21 session (Presentation): Managing Windows with SaltStack Config&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(6) of my personal Blogs were shared by the VMware “vExpert Cloud Management Community” on the Vmware Blog Web Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did several vRealize Automation Presentations at VMware HVC (Healthcare Virtualization Community) Events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PowerBlock Customer Showcase - VM “Right Sizing”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did a IDC interview for VMware on Automation that will be released in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did a VMware Customer Reference Interview that will be released in 2022. &lt;a href=&#34;https://blogs.vmware.com/management/2022/03/vra-optimize-healthcare-outcomes.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Link to Customer Reference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I shared a vRealize Operations “Right Sizing” Dashboard on the code.vmware.com web site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-vmware-vexpert-program&#34;&gt;What is the VMware vExpert Program?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;program-overview&#34;&gt;Program Overview
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The VMware vExpert program is VMware&amp;rsquo;s global evangelism and advocacy program. The program is designed to put VMware&amp;rsquo;s marketing resources towards your advocacy efforts. Promotion of your articles, exposure at our global events, co-op advertising, traffic analysis, and early access to beta programs and VMware&amp;rsquo;s roadmap. The awards are for individuals, not companies, and last for one year. Employees of both customers and partners can receive the awards. In the application, we consider various community activities from the previous year as well as the current year&amp;rsquo;s (only for 2nd half applications) activities in determining who gets awards. We look to see that not only were you active but are still active in the path you chose to apply for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;criteria&#34;&gt;Criteria
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in becoming a vExpert the criteria is simple. We are looking for IT Professionals who are sharing their VMware knowledge and contributing that back to the community. The term &amp;ldquo;giving back&amp;rdquo; is defined as going above and beyond your day job. There are several ways to share your knowledge and engage with the community. Some of those activities are blogging, book authoring, magazine articles, CloudCred task writing, active in Facebook groups, forum (VMTN as well as other non VMware) platforms, public speaking, VMUG leadership, videos and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;thanks&#34;&gt;Thanks:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have worked with a great group of people at VMware, past and present. I would like to thank the following people for all their support in no particular order: Steve Leiberson, Karl Hauck, Cosmin Trif, Brock Peterson, Kevin Holland, Daniel Thomas, Marcus Roberts, Paul Schlosser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Thanks to David Kruse for getting me started with vRA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Thanks to some past co-workers, SEs, TAMs, HVC Members that I learned a lot from: Kirk Shaffer, Robert Mitchell, Dan Grove, Steve Holmes, Steve Pittenger, Anton Wesztergom (Opened my eyes to vRA Day 2).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;List of Bloggers that I follow and have learned a lot by them &amp;ldquo;Giving Back&amp;rdquo;: Cody De Arkland, Luc Dekens, Kyle Ruddy, William Lam, Nathen Bennett, Vince Wood, Alan Renouf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Thanks to the person that gave me my first Job in IT: David Cornelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and anyone else that helped me in my journey called my career&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have learned a lot from the vCommunity. I want to use this blog as a way for me to &amp;ldquo;give back&amp;rdquo;. If one person finds anything I post helpful I will consider my efforts successful. I am always open to talking to any person, group or organization about what I do with VMware products.  Please reach out to me if you ever want to have a discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mailto:Dale.Hassinger@vCrocs.info&#34; &gt;Dale.Hassinger@vCrocs.info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Location: Dillsburg, PA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;background-color:#ffcc80; Padding:20px; font-size:18px;&#34; &gt;
  &lt;b&gt;&#34;9 - 5 pays the bills, 5 - 10 advances your career&#34;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
