<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Goals on Dale Hassinger</title>
        <link>https://vcrocs.info/tags/goals/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Goals on Dale Hassinger</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>vCROCS</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vcrocs.info/tags/goals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>End of Year Review - 2023</title>
        <link>https://vcrocs.info/end-of-year-review-2023/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://vcrocs.info/end-of-year-review-2023/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://vcrocs.info/end-of-year-review-2023/featured-image.png" alt="Featured image of post End of Year Review - 2023" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End Of Year Review 2023&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The year 2023 was a good chapter in my career, emphasizing the importance of community contribution. I hold a belief that my endeavors are worthwhile if they benefit even one person. This past year, I engaged in numerous presentations and blog posts, focusing on giving back to the vCommunity. My efforts in sharing knowledge and resources have, I believe, positively impacted others, making 2023 a year of success and meaningful community engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;highlights-of-2023&#34;&gt;Highlights of 2023
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Started a VMware Aria Suite Solution Architect Role. I get to work with some people that have been role models to me. The culture within this Team is the best that I have ever experienced.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vExpert 2023 | Member since 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vExpert 2023 | vExpert Cloud Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMware Explore 2023 Hackathon: I was the Hackathon Team Lead and we finished 2nd place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMware Explore 2023 session (Presentation): Use VMware Aria to Create/Manage/Monitor Windows Servers (on-prem/cloud) [CODE2501LV]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The VMware Community Podcast | I was a Guest on the show.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The PowerShell Podcast | I was a Guest on the show&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Philly VMUG Presentation | VMware Aria Automation and Operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-top-20-blog-posts-of-2023&#34;&gt;My Top 20 Blog Posts of 2023
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Rank&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Blog Topic&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Views&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;vCROCS - Home Page&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3061&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;02&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Aria Automation and Ansible Integration&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1227&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;03&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Operations - Automation Central - Snapshot Age&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;713&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;04&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Aria Automation - Working with Windows Server Drives&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;660&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Automation Config API&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;574&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;How vRealize Operations can help with Right Sizing VMs&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;509&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Aria Automation and SaltStack Config Resource&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;380&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;08&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Aria Operations - RVTools Dashboard&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;331&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;09&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;How to use PowerShell Modules with vRA 8.2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;305&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Operations - Metric Search&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;291&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Operations - October 2023 PowerBlock&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;290&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Aria Operations - Servicenow - Management Pack&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;265&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;13&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Schedule RVTools Data Export&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;250&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;14&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Rest API calls in VMware Aria Automation with PowerShell&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;228&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Explore 2023 - Presentation&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;208&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Automation - ABX Action Constants and Secrets&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;166&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Automation - Custom Form Versioning&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;156&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;18&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Aria Operations for Logs (SaaS) - ESXi Host syslog setting&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;146&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Unlocking the Potential - VMware Aria Operations - Automation Central - VM Snaps&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;131&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VMware Explore 2023 - Hackathon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;125&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top 20 list reveals a significant interest in utilizing Automation and Operations. The fact that Ansible&amp;rsquo;s integration with VMware Aria Automation ranked #1 was unexpected, evidenced by the frequent views of this particular blog post. This observation has inspired me to dedicate more of my blogging efforts to VMware Aria Automation Ansible integration in the upcoming year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Stats from Google Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;set-goals-2024&#34;&gt;Set-Goals 2024
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give back more to the vCommunity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a good mentor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get a session approved for VMware Explore 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do more VMware Aria Presentations | PowerBlocks | Videos | etc&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create more Blog Posts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never Stop Learning&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;thanks-for-visiting-in-2023&#34;&gt;Thanks for visiting in 2023!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you found this Blog site useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js&#34; data-name=&#34;bmc-button&#34; data-slug=&#34;dalehassinger&#34; data-color=&#34;#FFDD00&#34; data-emoji=&#34;&#34;  data-font=&#34;Cookie&#34; data-text=&#34;Buy me a coffee&#34; data-outline-color=&#34;#000000&#34; data-font-color=&#34;#000000&#34; data-coffee-color=&#34;#ffffff&#34; &gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Year in Review - 2021 | 2022 Goals</title>
        <link>https://vcrocs.info/year-in-review-2021-2022-goals/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://vcrocs.info/year-in-review-2021-2022-goals/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://vcrocs.info/year-in-review-2021-2022-goals/featured-image.png" alt="Featured image of post Year in Review - 2021 | 2022 Goals" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get-Review 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2021 was a good year for me with my career. I spent the entire year working from home and I find myself to be more productive when WFH. My wife and I moved into a different home and I now have a dedicated office area on the 2nd floor away from everyone. I still share my office with Belle (Rescue Dog adopted in 2020 before covid) everyday and she loves the fenced in back yard that she can run around in without a leash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2021, I started living the &amp;ldquo;Salt Life&amp;rdquo;. In July, I installed SaltStack Config for the first time and started taking a serious look at Salt. I went from zero to doing a presentation about SaltStack at VMworld 2021 in October and another presentation at SaltConf21 in November. Having a session selected for VMworld 2021 was a career &amp;ldquo;Bucket List&amp;rdquo; for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After creating a vRealize Operations Dashboard on &amp;ldquo;Right Sizing&amp;rdquo; that I use in production, my vRealize Account Executive setup a meeting for me to meet Iwan &amp;rsquo;e1&amp;rsquo; Rahabok, who is the co-creator of the book &amp;ldquo;Operationalize Your World&amp;rdquo;. Iwan liked the Dashboard I created and included some details about the Dashboard in his book &amp;ldquo;Operationalize Your World&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always say if one person finds anything I post helpful, I will consider my efforts successful. In 2021, between the presentations and blogs posts, I feel I have given back and helped some people. I shared the knowledge.  2021 was a successful year for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;highlights-of-2021&#34;&gt;Highlights of 2021
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMworld 2021 session (Presentation): Manage Windows Workloads Through vRealize Automation SaltStack Config [MCL1895]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SaltConf21 session (Presentation): Managing Windows with SaltStack Config&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(6) of my personal Blogs were shared by the VMware &amp;ldquo;vExpert Cloud Management Community&amp;rdquo; on the Vmware Blog Web Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did several vRealize Automation Presentations at VMware HVC (Healthcare Virtualization Community) Events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PowerBlock Customer Showcase - VM &amp;ldquo;Right Sizing&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did a IDC interview for VMware on Automation that will be released in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did a VMware Customer Reference Interview that will be released in 2022. &lt;a href=&#34;https://blogs.vmware.com/management/2022/03/vra-optimize-healthcare-outcomes.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Link to Customer Reference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I shared a vRealize Operations &amp;ldquo;Right Sizing&amp;rdquo; Dashboard on the code.vmware.com web site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-top-10-blog-posts-of-2021&#34;&gt;My Top 10 Blog Posts of 2021
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to use PowerShell modules with vRA 8.2 | 978&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How vRealize Operations can help with &amp;ldquo;Right sizing&amp;rdquo; VMs | 799&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vRA 8.1 ABX PS | 508&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automating Automation | 415&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 1 | 333&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 2 | 280&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vRealize automation 8.1 PowerShell abx | 216&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 4 | 195&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin  part 6 | 164&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VMworld 2021 SaltStack Config session | 147&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What the top 10 list shows me is there is a lot of interest to use PowerShell with the vRealize Products, VMware admins are interested in Right Sizing and since VMware Purchased SaltStack people what to get started with the product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Stats from Google Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;set-goals-2022&#34;&gt;Set-Goals 2022
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I do a lot of posts on PowerShell and I use it everyday. I want to take some time in 2022 and learn Python. I have done a little bit of Python but not enough to call myself a Python Programmer. I think there are some use cases with vRealize Automation and SaltStack Config that knowing Python may help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I want to spend more time with Salt. Salt is a powerful tool and I want to expand my knowledge with Salt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get a session approved for VMworld 2022 and SaltConf22.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do more VMware PowerBlock Presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create more Blog Posts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never Stop Learning&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;thanks-for-visiting-in-2021&#34;&gt;Thanks for visiting in 2021!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js&#34; data-name=&#34;bmc-button&#34; data-slug=&#34;dalehassinger&#34; data-color=&#34;#FFDD00&#34; data-emoji=&#34;&#34;  data-font=&#34;Cookie&#34; data-text=&#34;Buy me a coffee&#34; data-outline-color=&#34;#000000&#34; data-font-color=&#34;#000000&#34; data-coffee-color=&#34;#ffffff&#34; &gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to be successful with VMware vRealize Products in your environment</title>
        <link>https://vcrocs.info/how-to-be-successful-with-vmware-vrealize-products-in-your-environment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://vcrocs.info/how-to-be-successful-with-vmware-vrealize-products-in-your-environment/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://vcrocs.info/how-to-be-successful-with-vmware-vrealize-products-in-your-environment/featured-image.png" alt="Featured image of post How to be successful with VMware vRealize Products in your environment" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to be successful with VMware vRealize Products in your environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I often get asked to speak to different organizations about what I have accomplished with the VMware vRealize Suite of products. The one question that almost always gets asked is, how are you able to do everything that you have setup in your environment.  After being asked this question a lot I thought I would give my thoughts in a Blog Post. Here is my &lt;strong&gt;“Recipe for Success”:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy what you do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give Back. Be involved in the vCommunity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy where you work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy who you work with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work at a place where management supports you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t be afraid of change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always keep track of what the industry is doing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Social Media like Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setup a Home Lab&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn, Learn, Learn!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think outside of the box&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;directions&#34;&gt;Directions:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most important ingredient is to enjoy what you do. I have worked in the IT industry for 25+ years and I still have a Passion for it. I feel that I get paid to do my hobby. I am fascinated every day when I see some of the new technology that get released. There are some very smart people in the IT industry. I can truly say that I love what do for a job! When I create Automation that makes processes consistent and faster for the Team that I work with, I get a feeling that I have accomplished something. “Feel Good”/’Proud” feeling inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attend and Participate in user groups. VMUG, “Little Hacks”, SQL, HVC, PowerBlocks, Under The Hoods, etc&amp;hellip;  I started out by just attending and learning. I met a lot of people at the user groups.  I now consider some of those people friends. After several years of being an attendee, I felt like I wanted to Give Back and start sharing some of the ideas that I have done.  So, I started doing presentations myself. Everyone has something to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work for a Team that isn’t afraid of change. I say tear down the “Silos” and have everyone work together more. I have heard people say that Automation will eliminate my job.  If you are an engineer, Automation will get the mundane items off your list. Let you focus more on Engineering type of tasks. The Cool Stuff!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;vRA: Start simple.  Don&amp;rsquo;t try and have a 100 processes in your first Catalog item. Keep adding additional steps to the Catalog item until you cross off everything that needs to be done. Prove to management that the simple Automation is working and being used every day. My Automation is in a constant state of change. Always trying to make it better. Constantly including new processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;vROPS: Start my making some simple Dashboards with Heat Maps that show the Health of Items.  Show your Hosts, VMs, Clusters. Start simple just like I said with Automation.  You can then keep adding widgets to the Dashboards to give more information and make them more useful. Look at the &amp;ldquo;Text Display&amp;rdquo; widget to let you show information not included within vROPS. Have a goal of using vROPS as your &amp;ldquo;Single Pane of Glass&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to conferences. In 2020 since almost all conferences were online and free, I attended at least 6.  Even if there was only one or two sessions that I wanted to attend, I took the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter is an awesome place to keep up. Use Twitter Lists to keep the “Garbage” out of you feed. I follow a lot of Technology businesses and Bloggers.  Find people that have similar interests. Tech Companies are always giving updates about their products on Twitter. They post information about webinars that I find very useful. My Twitter Lists are public if you want to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Setup a Lab area of some type to be able to learn all the vRealize Products. One way to get a Home Lab started is to use VMware Fusion on Macs or VMware Workstation on PC’s.  You can install nested ESXi on Fusion/Workstation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a Packt subscription that gives me access to a lot of Technology Books on a lot of topics. Well worth the money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting a Blog is a great way to start #GivingBack. Hugo is a great static site generator.  You can use Github at no cost to store and host the web pages generated from Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“9 – 5 pays the Bills. 5 – 10 advances your career.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#VMware | #vRealizeAuto | #saltstack | #vRealizeOPS | #vmloginsight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2022-update&#34;&gt;2022 Update:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had to make some changes in 2022. I was starting to miss some of the ingredients that I listed in this Blog post when I originally wrote it so I made a change in my career to get all the ingredients back. When you have a passion for what you do, don&amp;rsquo;t let other people take that drive to keep being successful away. A word that is very important to me is Respect. In my Blog posts I will list people that have helped me in my career. I respect and look up to all those names listed. Life is to short to not have Respect for what you do and have accomplished&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js&#34; data-name=&#34;bmc-button&#34; data-slug=&#34;dalehassinger&#34; data-color=&#34;#FFDD00&#34; data-emoji=&#34;&#34;  data-font=&#34;Cookie&#34; data-text=&#34;Buy me a coffee&#34; data-outline-color=&#34;#000000&#34; data-font-color=&#34;#000000&#34; data-coffee-color=&#34;#ffffff&#34; &gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
