<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>POSH-SSH on vCROCS.info</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/posh-ssh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in POSH-SSH on vCROCS.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/tags/posh-ssh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 7</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2022/01/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-7/</guid>
      <description>Part 7:
The more I use VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin the more I see the importance of having grain information added to the minion to be able to target servers many different ways. During a recent discussion it was suggested to have the ability to target Windows Server minions by the Windows server Features|Roles that were installed on the server and by which software was installed on a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 6</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-6/</guid>
      <description>Part 6:
        The latest item on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin is going to be a lot PowerShell. I use PowerShell for a lot of Automation, Windows Server and Linux Server. When working with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config I constantly found myself going to the CLI to test and learn how the salt functions work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/2021/10/vmware-vrealize-saltstack-config-as-a-windows-server-admin-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Part 5:
 The latest item on my journey with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config as a Windows Server Admin will be an update to some items that I have talked about in previous posts. I have been spending more time with VMware vRealize SaltStack Config and I have learned some better ways to do some of the processes that I have talked about already. My goal to to learn and use the built-in functions that are already in the product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
