<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Home Lab - Category - vCROCS</title>
        <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/categories/home-lab/</link>
        <description>Home Lab - Category - vCROCS</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Dale.Hassinger@vCROCS.info (| Dale Hassinger)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vcrocs.info/categories/home-lab/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How to learn about VMware Products</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>How to learn about and use VMware Products in a Home Lab</strong></p>
<hr>
<p>I was inspired to create this Blog after VMware EOA (End of Availability) the free ESXi product. There were some articles saying that people just getting into IT Technology roles will now not be able to learn about VMware Products. This is <strong>NOT True</strong> and I wanted to share some examples of how people can still learn about Virtualization with VMware Products in a Home Lab environment.</p>
<hr>
<p>I have been in the IT Industry for many years and there is a quote that I use all the time for people that want to advance their IT skills. &ldquo;9 - 5 pay the bills but 5 - 10 advances your career&rdquo;.</p>
<p><strong>There are still many options to learn about VMware Products. Here are some items that can be used to advance your knowledge:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>VMware Workstation | <a href="https://www.vmware.com/products/workstation-player.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to Workstation Download site</a></li>
<li>VMware Fusion | <a href="https://www.vmware.com/products/fusion.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to Fusion Download site</a></li>
<li>VMware ESXi  <a href="https://www.vmware.com/products/vsphere.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to vSphere Download site</a></li>
<li>Vmware ESXi ARM Edition | <a href="https://communities.vmware.com/t5/ESXi-Arm-Fling-Documents/VMware-ESXi-Arm-Documentation/ta-p/2993062" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to Documentation</a></li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p>You also don&rsquo;t need to have the newest, fastest, most advanced hardware if you just want to learn about the VMware Products.  The hardware I have to create this Blog Post is an older Apple MacBook Pro that is no longer supported and will not run the latest versions of MAC OS. I installed Ubuntu Desktop on this Apple Laptop and then installed VMware Workstation. This setup is OK for learning and testing. I have a Raspberry PI 4 with 8 GB memory to install ESXi ARM Edition.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Items to know when setting up a Home Lab environment:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>VMware ESXi | Default Evaluation period is 60 days. This will enable you to have a full featured host to test anything you want to learn for 60 days.</li>
<li>VMware Workstation | Non-Commercial use is free to use</li>
<li>VMware Fusion | Non-Commercial use is free to use</li>
<li>Vmware ESXi ARM Edition | Default Evaluation period is 180 days</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p><strong>To get access to additional VMware Software, Take a look at VMUG Advantage:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.vmug.com/membership/evalexperience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Link to VMUG Advantage</a></li>
<li>You do have to purchase VMUG Advantage. If you attend a local VMUG event, you will often get coupons for a discount to purchase VMUG Advantage.</li>
<li>This is one of the best vCommunity Programs you can join and it will include licenses for many of the VMware solutions which are valid for a year.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h6 id="vmware-workstation">VMware Workstation</h6>
<p>Screen Shot of my MacBook Pro Resources. Doesn&rsquo;t need to be latest and greatest to learn.<br>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/learn-01.png" title="/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/learn-01.png" data-thumbnail="/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/learn-01.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</figcaption>
    </figure></p>
<p>Screen Shot of VMware Workstation running a Ubuntu Server. Great way to learn.
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/learn-02.png" title="/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/learn-02.png" data-thumbnail="/how-to-learn-about-vmware-products/learn-02.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image of Screen Shot</figcaption>
    </figure></p>
<hr>
<div class="details admonition info open">
        <div class="details-summary admonition-title">
            <i class="icon fas fa-info-circle fa-fw" aria-hidden="true"></i>Info<i class="details-icon fas fa-angle-right fa-fw" aria-hidden="true"></i>
        </div>
        <div class="details-content">
            <div class="admonition-content">When I write my blogs, I always say there are many ways to accomplish the same task. This article is just one way that you could accomplish this task. I am showing what I felt was a good way to complete the use case but every organization/environment will be different. There is no right or wrong way to complete the tasks in this article.</div>
        </div>
    </div>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>
<hr>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Smart Desk and Homelab.</title>
    <link>https://www.vcrocs.info/standup-desk/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Dale Hassinger</author>
    <guid>https://www.vcrocs.info/standup-desk/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Working from Home | My New Homelab.</strong></p>
<hr>
<hr>
<h6 id="smart-desk">Smart Desk:</h6>
<p>Like most people that work in the Technology Field, I have been &ldquo;WFH&rdquo; (Working From Home) since the beginning of March. I already had a dedicated office area but it wasn’t setup for full time employment. I always liked a L-Shaped desk and I had this layout by pushing to straight desks together. Worked OK but could use improvement.</p>
<p>So I started looking at new desks.  I had two requirements, L-Shaped and I also wanted my next desk to be a standup Desk. I reviewed a lot of desks online and I decided to go with the <a href="https://www.autonomous.ai/standing-desks/l-shaped-smartdesk" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">L-Shaped Smart Desk from Autonomous</a>. I am the type of person that usually likes to “touch and feel” this type of purchase to make sure the quality is good but after reviewing what other people were saying about <a href="https://www.autonomous.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Autonomous</a> I decided to make the purchase. My biggest concern was damage during shipping.</p>
<hr>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/standup-desk/smartdesk01.png" title="/standup-desk/smartdesk01.png" data-thumbnail="/standup-desk/smartdesk01.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image</figcaption>
    </figure>
<hr>
<p>When the desk was delivered I was impressed by how well the desk was packaged.  <a href="https://www.autonomous.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Autonomous</a> does a great job making sure nothing gets damaged.  Everything arrived OK and there was no damage or missing pieces. The desk is heavy to put together by yourself.  I took my time so I wouldn’t damage anything and the process to assemble was very easy.  The directions were good. All the holes in the top are pre-drilled, which make it very nice to align all the pieces. The corners on the top are all slightly rounded and the edges are all eased.  That really adds to the look and feel.  I was impressed. I’m sure this also helps in shipping so that the top doesn’t get damaged. The quality of the top is so nice that a mouse does not work without a mouse pad.  I did have to purchase a mouse pad to use with this desk. A black mouse pad on a black top looks good.  I like the wire management included with the desk. I think I will be ordering a couple of the <a href="https://www.autonomous.ai/office-accessories/power-outlet" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Autonomous Desk Clamp Power Outlets</a> to make wire management even better. All my Apple Space Grey items look good on the Black top. I am anxious to see how often I will use the desk while standing and if I will like to be standing while programming. There is enough room on the L-Shaped desk to hold (3) monitors, (2) Mac Mini’s, external drives, iPad, iPhone, MacBook Pro, AirPods, HomePod, Microsoft Surface Pro, Dell Work Laptop, Shure Mic and a Google Home (Yes I am an Apple Fanboy).  Happy with my Smart Desk decision.</p>
<hr>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/standup-desk/smartdesk02.png" title="/standup-desk/smartdesk02.png" data-thumbnail="/standup-desk/smartdesk02.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image</figcaption>
    </figure>
<hr>
<h6 id="vmware-home-lab">VMware Home Lab:</h6>
<p>In addition to upgrading my Home Office Desk, it was time to upgrade my VMware Home Lab. My HPE GEN 6 DL380 was not on the VMware supported hardware list anymore and generated a lot of heat and noise in the Home Office.</p>
<p>I already had an Apple Mac Mini with VMware Fusion installed but it didn’t have a lot of memory installed.  I used it to run some small VMs but mainly used the DL380 for my Homelab. So I upgraded the memory on the Mac mini to 64 GB. I also purchased a second Mac Mini and upgraded the memory to 64 GB. So now my Homelab consists of (2) Mac Mini’s with a total of 128 GB memory.  I have multiple nested ESXi 7.0 Hosts installed on each Mac Mini using VMware Fusion. The setup has worked well for me so far.  No noise and heat like I had with the DL380. Plus I can use the Mac Mini’s for more than just a Homelab.  Turn on the ESXi Hosts when needed and then just power off to do my normal everyday computing. If I don’t want to run the VMs on ESXi, I can also just run VMs directly on Fusion.</p>
<hr>
<figure><a class="lightgallery" href="/standup-desk/homelab01.png" title="/standup-desk/homelab01.png" data-thumbnail="/standup-desk/homelab01.png" data-sub-html="<h2>Click to see Larger Image</h2>">
        
    </a><figcaption class="image-caption">Click to see Larger Image</figcaption>
    </figure>
<hr>
<p>So a month after making my Home Lab work with Apple Mac Mini’s, Apple decides to make all new Apple computers with ARM processors. I guess my next Home Lab upgrade will not be Apple Computers. I will probably look at using Intel NUCs or something like the NUC for my next Home Lab.</p>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>If you like wearing Crocs and want to get a pair like I wear, follow this link to Amazon:
<a target="_blank" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001V7Z27W?psc=1&amp;ref=ppx_yo2ov_dt_b_product_details&_encoding=UTF8&tag=vcrocs-20&linkCode=ur2&linkId=fa4c787c9ab59a9b8a54b48c402b8517&camp=1789&creative=9325">My Favorite Crocs</a></li>
<li>If you found this Blog article useful and it helped you, Buy me a coffee to start my day.</li>
</ul>
<center>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://cdnjs.buymeacoffee.com/1.0.0/button.prod.min.js" data-name="bmc-button" data-slug="dalehassinger" data-color="#FFDD00" data-emoji=""  data-font="Cookie" data-text="Buy me a coffee" data-outline-color="#000000" data-font-color="#000000" data-coffee-color="#ffffff" ></script>
</center>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
